Alright now that we've planted the seed, we want to take the rake here, make sure there's no weeds still hanging out in the bed after moving the dirt around a little bit.
We want to get rid of the weeds, so we can tell the difference between the lettuce that comes up.
We don't want to have any weeds in the way.
We'll pull a few more of these weeds out of the way and were going to rake it in.
Now with lettuce it doesn't like to be covered up with dirt too much, just wants to be raked in.
These rows here that I've put in rows we're just to lightly rake around just to get some dirt over top of them.
Lettuce seeds need light in order to germinate, so we don't want to cover them up.
Now once we rake it.
We're just going to take the rake and secure the dirt a little bit there nice and packed down.
Alright there we go